Halil Çağrı Bilgi

hcagri98@gmail.com +90 5073799446 Ankara, Turkey hcagri.github.io



Summary

Machine Learning Engineer whose main research area is computer vision, specifically multiple object tracking. Also competent both in literature and practice of deep generative models, and deep learning on graphs. Competitive Python programmer, fast learner, and a team member. For more information please refer to here.

Experience

Research Assistant

Middle East Technical University - Ankara, Turkey

11/2022 - Present

Teaching Assistant: Involved in teaching Digital Signal Processing, Digital Circuit Laboratory.

Graduate Researcher

OGAM - Ankara, Turkey

09/2021 - Present

- Conducts research on tracklet merging algorithms using graph-based deep learning methods for Multiple Object
 Tracking. Re-implements or adapts state-of-the-art methods to a given problem. Also experimenting with Optimal
 Transport Theory in Tracklet Merging problem.
- Participated in an international project funded by Telespazio to estimate the positions and orbits of space objects utilizing images. Building a pipeline that includes orbit determination, propagation, and refinement.

Software Engineer

MILSOFT - Ankara, Turkey

04/2021 - 08/2021

 Developed image processing algorithms for SAR imagery using OpenCV and PyTorch. Implemented methods from the literature using PyTorch.

Education

MSc, Electrical Electronics Eng. - Signal Processing / Machine Learning

Middle East Technical University - Ankara, Turkey

Expected in 2024

- Thesis Study: Graph-based Multiple Object Tracking
- GPA: 3.86
- · Taken Courses:
 - · Deep Learning
 - Deep Generative Models
 - Machine Vision

- Advance Deep Learning
- Pattern Recognition
- Statistical Signal Processing and Modeling

BSc, Electrical Electronics Eng. - Signal Processing

Middle East Technical University - Ankara, Turkey

07/2021

- · Specialized on Signal Processing Area
- GPA: 3.12

Languages

English: Professional Working Proficiency - C1 (IELTS 8.0/9)

German: Elementary - A2

Turkish: Native

Skills

Deep Learning, Machine Learning, Python, PyTorch, GANs, GNNs, C++, Pandas, Numpy, SQL, TensorFlow, Statistics